for for the for the NFL. Like at Ohio
State,
I I was so accustomed to competing every
day that this is what I do. I I expect
it.
>> I know you cut down considerably out
there last year. What part of your game
did you feel you most effectively change
to keep the flags?
>> Um I would just say I just played with
poise at the top of the route. Like I
had to watch what I was doing wrong. I
realized that like I wasn't getting
beat, wasn't people weren't running past
me. I was in great positions a lot of
the time. Those PI should have been PBUS
and interceptions. So, I just watched it
in 2024 and 2025. Just relaxed when the
ball was in the air, got my head around,
made plays on the football.
>> Have you had time to process being
drafted? I know it's been a whirlwind
probably since we talked to you last
night and then coming up here, but like
have you had any chance for those
emotions to settle? And if so, what has
that been like?
>> No, I haven't. You know, like this is a
dream. Like right now, this moment, I
feel like I'm living a dream. Like I'm
right I'm sitting up here getting
interviewed by a bunch of media
personnel. So I feel like I'm in a like
I'm in a video game right now. Like
seriously. But I'm just blessed. Like of
course as as a young man, as a kid, like
I visualize, I dream for this and the
fact that everything's coming to
fruition is just a blessing.
>> At Ohio State, you had the opportunity
to practice against some of the best
receivers in the country. What were how
did you sort of hone your game going
against those guys?
>> Um yeah, that was the whole point of me
going to Ohio State. I wanted to go to
Ohio State because at the time they had
Marvin up there. He was the best
receiver in college football show. I'm
like why would I not go against Marvin
every single day? Like if I'm having a
good day or a bad day, still got to line
up against him. Um I would What was the
question again?
>> How did you improve through that
process?
>> Yeah. So iron sharpens iron. So, so as
as another man sharpens another man, if
you if you go against the best every
day, if you want to become the best, you
have to go against the best and beat the
best. So, that's that was the whole
point. Like, if I'm going against top
guys, that's going to make me a top guy.
>> How did you go about cutting down on
penalties? Were you studying your own
tape and and how dedicated did you
become over that off season to to to cut
that down and and knowing that you were
improving yourself?
>> Yeah. Um, I studied my own tape cuz I
had to like I had to study myself, see
what I was doing wrong, seeing what I
had to improve on. And um, I would just
say like that's just what I do. Like
this game that's not about even just me
as a football player, just kind of
person I am. I just want to be the best
version of myself that I possibly can.
So, I'm willing to do whatever it takes
to become better, become the best
version of myself. So, um, wouldn't want
to say I obsessed over it, but a lot of
like the narrative in 2024 was like he's
grabby whatnot. I'm like, it's not
that's not that's not who I am. It's not
my game. I wanted to change the
narrative. So, I understood I had to put
the work in if I wanted to change the
narrative.
>> To know that the Bills moved up a few
spots for you really kind of shows that
they prioritized making sure that they
were able to select you. What is What
does that mean to you?
>> Um, it means the world to me because I
think highly of myself and to see a
organization think highly of me. It it
it just validates everything that I
thought about myself. Um, and I would
say they just
they gave me they blessed me with the
opportunity and I'm going to do
everything that I can to make sure I
maximize the opportunity and and just
and just be the best version I can for
this organization that drafted me.
>> IGB, uh, two questions. First, how much
have you gotten to know Jim Leonard at
all through this process? And number
two, can you just talk about tackling at
the NFL level as a physical guy and, you
know, what you bring to the table in
that regard? Yeah, I would say uh coach
Leonard uh he played 10 years in the
NFL. A lot a lot of coaches do that. So
immediately when I Jordan Hancock told
me that I didn't even know that. Soon as
he told me that, I Googled him and
searched him up and he was a good
football player. So I just I I respect
him his his his mindset as a coach and I
respect his ability when he played as a
player.
>> Yeah, I know. Um I would say just my
mentality tackling the NFL. I tackle my
whole life. I'm like I'm not afraid of
anybody. I put my face in the fan. What
I feel like that that that is one of the
reasons that separates me from the other
corners in the country. If you try try
to run the football at me, I'm going to
down the football. Like that's what I
take pride in.
>> Have you gotten to talk to Jordan at
all? I saw he posted a lot about you.
Excited.
>> Yeah. Um I spoke to him. I haven't had a
in-depth conversation, but he called me.
My mom passed me the phone last night
and he's yelling in my face. I'm yelling
at him, so I didn't hear anything, but
it's just mad love. Just me and Jordan's
relationship. how much like we've grown
at Ohio State, I I got into Ohio State
and I had to compete with him
immediately. Like the the corner two
spot wasn't locked up. So, it was just
me versus Jordan. So, we kind of when I
walked in were kind of going against
each other. Like, we didn't have beef,
but we were competitors. Like, he I
wanted the job and he wanted the job.
So, over time over time, me and him con
constantly keep going against each
other. We we at the end of training
camp, we we we shook each other's hands
and said like, "Yo, I I I respect you as
a football player. I respect your game."
So that after that we just develop a
true and real friendship.
>> Do you think having a guy like that here
will be an an aid to you and assistant?
>> Yeah, that's going to help me
tremendously. Just going to I'm going to
just soak the game up from him cuz he
was literally in this position a year
ago. So I'm just going to follow him
around and just just
they they also speak very highly of
Jordan here in this organization. So I'm
just going to follow him around and just
learn the rope from him. might be uh I
got a lot of friends from Jersey and it
just seems like it's just like Jersey
then it's just the rest of the United
States. Just kind of talk about you know
your bringing in that jersey.
>> Yeah, it's Jersey versus the world. Um
if you ask me I would say uh just
playing in college football I've been
around. Um New Jersey doesn't get the
respect that New Jersey deserves. Like,
and another thing, a lot of when when
kids are in high school, a lot a lot of
public school kids don't get recruited
because cuz college coaches come and and
they only stay in the big nerf and they
don't really recruit the public public
school kids. So, a lot of kids are are
often just not seen or and are often
like just they have the talent but are
just not found. So, I would just say
like growing up in New Jersey, you got
to be tough. and and and me growing up
in New Jersey has allowed me to just be
here, be in this moment just and just
has prepared me for an environment, a
competitive uh uh environment like the
NFL.
>> Can can you take us through yesterday
and like going into the draft? Did you
have kind of like an idea of maybe where
you can go and when that call came in? I
mean, how surprised were you based on
what your expectations were? Yeah, like
I said, I I think very highly of myself.
So, I don't allow other people's uh
expectations of me have an effect on me.
So, I thought I thought and I felt like
I should go yesterday. Like, I can go
yesterday, but my agent called me. He's
like he's he's trying to he's trying to
have me like prepare for the worst, you
know? But I'm like, I serve a living
God. I'm not I don't care what anybody
else says, what any man has to say. I
know that like I'm I'm ready for this.
Like, I'm supposed to be here. So, like
I invited friends over, family over, put
on a nice outfit, and then when I'm
doing all this, this is me betting on
myself cuz I'm not going to invite
everybody over to my house and put on a
nice outfit and not get my name called.
So, I just trusted the Lord. Just walked
in faith. I knew it was going to work
out.
>> You You're a Northeast kid. Do you like
hockey at all? The uh owner owns both
the Sabres and the Bills here.
>> I didn't even know that. Um I like the
fights in hockey. I don't Yeah, I don't
watch too much hockey, though.
>> You're in a unique position. You guys
are part of the first draft class that's
going to play in the stadium across the
streets, the new stadium. I would
imagine these last like 20 hours have
been a complete whirlwind for you. Have
you thought about that at all? Like a
new era for the Bills and like see you
guys.
>> I thought about that when I was driving
in. They showed it to me on my 30 visit,
but I'm like, "Wow, new stadium, but you
know, a 30 visit is like a it's like a
OV. So like you're getting you're
talking to a lot of people. You don't
know if you're going to be here or like
actually be here." hear them when I'm
like, "Dang, I'm actually going to be
the f one of the first like first guys
on on the like first people to like play
in that stadium." It just it's a
blessing.
>> When you get drafted last night, did you
find out it's the Bills? Obviously, I
would imagine you immediately pick up
Jordan and then your time here.
>> Do you just start like googling players?
You go like watching YouTube clips. Like
what do you do when you find out, okay,
I'm interacted by the films? No, I
didn't do that because I came on a 30
visit, but like it was a it was a
different 30 visit just because I kind I
even slept at Jordan's house. Like I I
got I got immersed with the players. I I
I hung out with Max, hung out with uh
Strong. I got invol like I got around
the guys. Like I I was having lunch with
him. I'm like, man, I wouldn't be mad if
the Bills draft me. Like I I could see
myself here. So I didn't So I just felt
like this was a it was a a good group of
people. It's a good group of people in
this building.
>> Do you know who Nate Clemens and Antoine
Winfield are? Ohio State. They both
played here in Buffalo Corners. Uh
really big parts of the organization not
too long ago.
>> Sure.
>> Yeah. I don't know if you know who they
were.
>> I know. I know. I know of them.
>> They have a good They've had good track
record of, you know, guys from Ohio
State coming. Not sure if you knew that
or not.
>> Yes, sir.
>> You just met TJ Parker, you know. So,
what was that conversation like for the
first time?
>> Uh we just talked about just the
emotions of draft day. like it's it's
it's it's not it's not um a situation
that a lot of people in this world get
to feel like you're literally everything
that you've worked for your entire life.
It's like you're putting it on the line.
You're seeing if you're if if you are
who you think you are. So, we just
talking about that and chopping it up.
Just telling just telling each other
that like we're here to like win cuz
this cuz the Bills are a playoff
contender. Always in the playoffs, but
we want to pull up and get the job done.
Congratulations.